A Guide to the Records of the Office of Vice-President and the Office of Executive Vice-President, Warren W. Brandt, 1958-1969
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series II: 1965-1966
  - Optimization Committee, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 347)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 348)
  - Payne, Alfred, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 349)
  - Personnel Regulations, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 350)
  - Philosophy and Religion, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 351)
  - Physical Education Department, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 352)
  - Physics Department, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 353)
  - Placement and Guidance, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 354)
  - Placement Reports, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 355)
  - Plant Pathology, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 356)
  - Political Science Department, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 357)
  - Principal’s Committee, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 358)
  - Proposal - Graduate Incentive Fund, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 359)
  - Proposal - Graduate Incentive Fund, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 360)
  - Proposal - Graduate Incentive Fund, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 361)
  - Proposal - Graduate Incentive Fund, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 362)
  - Proposal - Graduate Incentive Fund, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 363)
  - Psychology and Sociology, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 364)
  - Psychology and Sociology, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 365)
  - Regional Educations Laboratory for the Carolinas and Virginia, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 366)
  - Research Division, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 367)
  - Roanoke Symphony, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 368)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 369)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 370)
  - R.O.T.C., 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 371)
  - Salary Information, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 372)
  - Schewe, Gen. M.W., 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 373)
  - Scholarships, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 374)
  - Selective service - Selective service regulations, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 375)
  - Sigma Xi, 1964-1967 (Box 10, Folder 376)
  - Social Sciences Committee, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 377)
  - Sporn Award, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 378)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 379)
  - State Technical Services Act, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 380)
  - State Technical Services Act, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 381)
  - Statistics Department, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 382)
  - Statistics Department, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 383)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 384)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 385)
  - Summer School, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 386)
  - Teaching-Learning Issues, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 387)
  - Tech Festival Association, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 388)
  - Tech Festival Association, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 389)
  - Thompson Ramo Woolridge, Inc., 1966 (Box 11, Folder 390)
  - Vet Science – Dr. Watson, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 391)
  - Virginia Academy of Science, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 392)
  - Virginia Association Research Center (VARC), 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 393)
  - VARC, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 394)
  - VARC, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 395)
  - VARC, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 396)
  - VARC, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 397)
  - VARC, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 398)
  - VARC, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 399)
  - VARC, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 400)
  - Visiting Scholar Program – College Scholars, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 401)
  - Visiting Scholar Program – University Scholars, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 402)
  - Visiting Scholar Program – University Scholars, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 403)
  - Visiting Scholar Program – University Scholars, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 404)
  - Visiting Scholar Program – College and Department Scholars, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 405)
  - Visiting Scholar Program – University Scholars, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 406)
  - Visiting Scholar Program – University Scholars, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 407)
  - Water Resources Research Institute, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 408)
  - Water Resources Research Institute, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 409)
  - Water Resources Research Institute, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 410)
  - Water Resources Research, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 411)
  - Wood Construction Department, 1963-1966 (Box 12, Folder 412)
  - Worcester, Willis G. Dean, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 413)
  - Worcester, Willis G. Dean, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 414)
  - Y.M.C.A., 1964-1966 (Box 12, Folder 415)
- Series III: 1967-1969
  - American Association of University Professors, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 416)
  - Academic Deans, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 417)
  - Admissions, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 418)
  - Aerospace Engineering, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 419)
  - Agency for International Development, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 420)
  - Agricultural Conference Board, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 421)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 422)
  - Agricultural Engineering, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 423)
  - Agricultural Engineering Study Committee, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 424)
  - Agronomy, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 425)
  - ALICE – Student Newspaper - Copies of an underground student newspaper, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 426)
  - Alumni Association, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 427)
  - Alumni Association, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 428)
  - American Council on Education, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 429)
  - Animal Science Department, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 430)
  - Appalachian Institute, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 431)
  - Art Department, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 432)
  - Associates, Visits and General Information, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 433)
  - Associates, Visits and General Information, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 434)
  - Athletics, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 435)
  - Athletics Association, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 436)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 437)
  - Basic Policy Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 438)
  - Basic Policy Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 439)
  - Behavioral and Social Sciences Survey Committee, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 440)
  - Bell, Wilson B., 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 441)
  - Berea College Enclosures, Appalachian Institute - Information on a conference on poverty in Appalachia, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 442)
  - Biochemistry, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 443)
  - Biochemistry Department, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 444)
  - Biology Department, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 445)
  - Black Students’ Letters - Letter concerning Black student rights as well as information on educational programming concerning Black history, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 446)
  - Board of Visitors, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 447)
  - Bond issues, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 448)
  - Brandt, Congratulations, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 449)
  - Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 450)
  - Budget Preparation, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 451)
  - Building Committee, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 452)
  - Building Committee, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 453)
  - Building Committee, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 454)
  - Building Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 455)
  - Building Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 456)
  - Building Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 457)
  - Building Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 458)
  - Bull, Fred W., 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 459)
  - Burchard, Charles, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 460)
  - Burchard, Charles, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 461)
  - Campus Governance Program, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 462)
  - Capital Outlay, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 463)
  - Catalog Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 464)
  - Cassell, Stuart K., 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 465)
  - Centennial, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 466)
  - Center for Excellence Proposal Committee, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 467)
  - Center for Research in College Instruction in Science and Math, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 468)
  - Chairmen Meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 469)
  - Chemistry Department, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 470)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 471)
  - Civilian Intermediary Council, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 472)
  - Civil Engineering, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 473)
  - Coffee Payments, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 474)
  - College Committee on Advising, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 475)
  - Commencement, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 476)
  - Computer Committee, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 477)
  - Computer Committee, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 478)
  - Consulting, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 479)
  - Consulting, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 480)
  - Corps of Cadets, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 481)
  - Corps of Engineers Fellowship Program, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 482)
  - Council of Deans – Meetings, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 483)
  - Counseling Center, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 484)
  - Dairy Science Department, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 485)
  - Dean J.W. – V.P. Students - Letter concerning the playing of “Dixie” and the flying of the confederate flag at Virginia Tech sporting events, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 486)
  - Dean of Men - Letter concerning housing availability for women and African-Americans. (Box 14, Folder 487)
  - Dean of Women - Letter concerning the issue of interracial dating, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 488)
  - Dean of Students, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 489)
  - Dean of Students, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 490)
  - Dean of Students, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 491)
  - Dean of Students – Discipline, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 492)
  - Development Council, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 493)
  - Director of Development, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 494)
  - Department of Economics, 1965-1968 (Box 14, Folder 495)
  - Economics Department, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 496)
  - Department of Education, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 497)
  - Education Foundation, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 498)
  - EDUCOM, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 499)
  - EDUCOM, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 500)
  - EDUCOM – Interuniversity Communications Council, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 501)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 502)
  - Energy Research Group, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 503)
  - College of Engineering, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 504)
  - Engineering Mechanics, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 505)
  - Engineering Mechanics Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 506)
  - English – Speaking Union, 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 507)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 508)
  - Entomology Department, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 509)
  - ESSO – Education Foundation, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 510)
  - ESSO – Education Foundation, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 511)
  - Extension Division, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 512)
  - Extension Division, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 513)
  - Extension Division, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 514)
  - Extension Division, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 515)
  - Faculty Handbook Recommendations, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 516)
  - Faculty Handbook Recommendations, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 517)
  - Faculty Handbook Recommendations, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 518)
  - Faculty Senate Steering Committee, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 519)
  - Ferrum Junior College, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 520)
  - Foreign Languages Department, 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 521)
  - Foreign Scholars, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 522)
  - Foreign Study, 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 523)
  - Forestry and Wildlife, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 524)
  - Forestry and Wildlife, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 525)
  - Fraternities and Sororities Subcommittee, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 526)
  - Geology Department, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 527)
  - Glee Club, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 528)
  - Governor’s Day, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 529)
  - Grade Changes, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 530)
  - Grade Summary, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 531)
  - Graduate Committee Minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 532)
  - Graduate School, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 533)
  - Hahn, T. Marshall Jr., 1968 (Box 15, Folder 534)
  - Harper, Laura Jane, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 535)
  - Health, Education and Welfare Department, 1964-1969 (Box 15, Folder 536)
  - Health and Physical Education, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 537)
  - Higher Education Study Commission, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 538)
  - History Department, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 539)
  - Honor Court, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 540)
  - Horticulture Department, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 541)
  - Housing Conference, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 542)
  - Industrial Engineering, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 543)
  - Information Services, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 544)
  - Institutional Research, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 545)
  - Institution Research, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 546)
  - Instructional Programs Advisory Committee, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 547)
  - International Education Committee, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 548)
  - International Programs, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 549)
  - Judicial Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 550)
  - Letter to the Lilliputians, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 551)
  - Library, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 552)
  - Library, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 553)
  - Library – Acquisitions, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 554)
  - Library Committee, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 555)
  - Malpass, Leslie F. Dean, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 556)
  - Malpass, Leslie F. Dean, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 557)
  - Malpass, Leslie F. Dean, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 558)
  - Martin, James E., 1968 (Box 15, Folder 559)
  - Mathematics Department, 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 560)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 561)
  - Military Affairs Committee, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 562)
  - Miscellaneous – Bulletins, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 563)
  - Miscellaneous – Letters, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 564)
  - Miscellaneous – Reports and Figures, 1964-1967 (Box 15, Folder 565)
  - Mitchell, H.H., 1967 (Box 15, Folder 566)
  - Mitchell, H.H. Dean, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 567)
  - Mitchell, H.H. Dean, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 568)
  - Montgomery County Study Group, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 569)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 570)
  - National Research Council, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 571)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1968 (Box 15, Folder 572)
  - NSF, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 573)
  - NSF, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 574)
  - NSF – Computer Proposal, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 575)
  - NSF – Departmental Science and Development Proposal for Geological Sciences, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 576)
  - NSF – Foreign Fellowship, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 577)
  - New Faculty, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 578)
  - New Faculty, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 579)
  - New Faculty, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 580)
  - Old Dominion College, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 581)
  - Orchestra, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 582)
  - Orientation Committee, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 583)
  - Parents, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 584)
  - Pass Fail letters 1969. (Box 16, Folder 585)
  - Personnel – Garber, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 586)
  - Physics Department, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 587)
  - Placement and Guidance, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 588)
  - Plant Pathology, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 589)
  - Plant Pathology Publications, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 590)
  - Political Science Department, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 591)
  - Poultry Science, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 592)
  - Presbyterian Church, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 593)
  - Promotions, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 594)
  - Promotions of Faculty, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 595)
  - Proposals, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 596)
  - Proposals, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 597)
  - Proposals, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 598)
  - Prospective Personnel, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 599)
  - Psychology, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 600)
  - Psychology and Sociology, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 601)
  - Quality Credit Averages, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 602)
  - Questionnaires, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 603)
  - Recommendations for Students, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 604)
  - Registrar – Keller, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 605)
  - Requisitions, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 606)
  - Requisitions – expenses and travel, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 607)
  - Research Council Meetings, 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 608)
  - Research Division, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 609)
  - Research Division, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 610)
  - Research Division, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 611)
  - Research Division, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 612)
  - Research Division, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 613)
  - Research Division, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 614)
  - Research Division – Monthly Reports, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 615)
  - Research Division – Monthly Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 616)
  - Richmond Professional Institute, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 617)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 618)
  - R.O.T.C., 1968 (Box 16, Folder 619)
  - Sabbaticals, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 620)
  - Sea Grant Program, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 621)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 622)
  - Sociology, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 623)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 624)
  - Southern Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 625)
  - State Board of Education, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 626)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 627)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 628)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 629)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 630)
  - Statements – Expenditures and Balances, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 631)
  - Statements – Expenditures and Balances, 0197-1968 (Box 17, Folder 632)
  - Statistics Department, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 633)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 634)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 635)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 636)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 637)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 638)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 639)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 640)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 641)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 642)
  - Student Activity Fee, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 643)
  - Student Budget Board, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 644)
  - Student Correspondence - Copies of underground student publications concerned with student rights, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 645)
  - Student Government Senate Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 646)
  - Student Government Senate Minutes, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 647)
  - Student Government Senate Minutes, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 648)
  - Student Leaders, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 649)
  - Student Life Committee, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 650)
  - Student Rights and Freedom, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 651)
  - Student Union, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 652)
  - Summer Orientation, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 653)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 654)
  - Tech United Ministries, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 655)
  - Themis Proposal, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 656)
  - TIAA-CREF, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 657)
  - Traffic Appeals Committee, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 658)
  - Travel Expense Vouchers, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 659)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 660)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 661)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 662)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 663)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 664)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 665)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 666)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 667)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 668)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 669)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 670)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 671)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 672)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 673)
  - University Council, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 674)
  - University Enterprises, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 675)
  - University Research, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 676)
  - Upward Bound, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 677)
  - Urban and Regional Studies, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 678)
  - Vandenburg, H.P.C., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 679)
  - Virginia Associated Research Center, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 680)
  - Vice Presidential Openings, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 681)
  - Visiting Scholar Honorariums, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 682)
  - Visiting Scholar Program, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 683)
  - Visiting Scholar Program, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 684)
  - Visiting Scholar Program – College and Department Scholars, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 685)
  - Visiting Scholar Program – College and Department Scholars, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 686)
  - Visiting Scholar Program – University Scholars, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 687)
  - Wallops Island Group, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 688)
  - Water Resources Research, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 689)
  - Worcester, W.G. Dean, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 690)
  - Worcester, W.G. Dean, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 691)
  - Worcester, W.G. Dean, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 692)